<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<overview>
	<bullet>
		<title>I just can't wait...</title>
		<date>July 2018</date>
		<description>
			I always tried to help people around, because I believe that "if you lift people up, they will lift you up". Indeed, what I am having right now all coming from the people that I helped. I got a good place to live. When I was in trouble, I was not alone. When I didn't have the money, someone gave me the money and told me to take it. They are my good friends - great people with missing pieces. I just gave them the pieces they need.
		</description>
		<description>
			My wife sometimes complained that "why did you do so many things for other people?". She doesn't understand how I enjoyed it, spent my time with the other, saw them happy with what I did for them.
		</description>
		<description>
			 However, at this moment, when I am at the place that I thought it fit me, things are so difficult. I tried to be helpful but they don't take it. I realized I am not welcome as usual. It is a little bit painful as I am not used to how people treated me that way.
		</description>
		<description>
			That's fine. I have been through many challenges and I am going to take it again. I will be stronger!
		</description>
		<image> </image>
	</bullet>


	<bullet>
		<title>I just can't wait...</title>
		<date>July 2018</date>
		<description>
			I just came back from work, my first job - a dishwasher. Sometimes, while I am washing the dishes, I wonder what I am doing right now?! I came to Canan with a strong mind, is ready to do big things. I know that I am getting there soon, but I just can't wait.
		</description>
		<description>
			 Over the last year, I have been doing so many things. I volunteered in many technology activities, worked as a Peer Tutor, an Education Assistant. I did all of those, but still maintain my good academic results and received some scholarships. I also worked as a researcher in ACE Project Space over this summer. Now I look back, what I have done so far is just getting myself accepted by this small city - Winnipeg.
		</description>
		<description>
			I recently shared my story with one of my favorite instructor - Carolyn. She is the one who helped me a lot when I started my new life in Canada. I told her about my plan to become an instructor, inspire and help the students like she did. She encouraged me that I am strong enough to do that. However, I knew I am not and I won't until I could achieve a great thing to inspire the people.
		</description>
		<description>
			 There is another thing, which I couldn't share with anyone. They might think that I am crazy, but I know what I can do. I want to be a master in the Technology world, where I can inspire the people, gather my own team and change the world. I already had many ideas for how I can form the future of this world, I am just waiting for the day I can do it.
		</description>
		<description>
			 I am 26, with a big dream of changing the world. As I mentioned, I am on the way getting accepted with many things undone. I might change in the future with a better plan or even become a normal employee just go to work for money.
		</description>
		<image>201807</image>
	</bullet>

	<bullet>
		<title>Moved to Canada</title>
		<date>July 2017</date>
		<description> </description>
		<image>201707</image>
	</bullet>

	<bullet>
		<title>Started working at Hella</title>
		<date>May 2016</date>
		<description> </description>
		<image>Hella</image>
	</bullet>
<!-- 	<bullet>
		<title>I just can't wait...</title>
		<date>January 2016</date>
		<description>First project in Data Science - SenseV2 - Object Oriented Estimation</description>
		<image>IMU</image>
	</bullet> -->
	<bullet>
		<title>Traveled to Singapore</title>
		<date>September 2015</date>
		<description> </description>
		<image>Singapore</image>
	</bullet>
	<bullet>
		<title>Freeline Skate</title>
		<date>July 2015</date>
		<description>Started riding Freeline Skate</description>
		<image>FreeLine</image>
	</bullet>
<!-- 	<bullet>
		<date>January 2015</date>
		<description>Designed and assembled my own gaming machine</description>
		<image>Game</image>
	</bullet> -->
	<bullet>
		<title>UAV industry - at VietSkyLine</title>
		<date>January 2014</date>
		<description>Got my first job - Embedded Developer in UAV industry - at VietSkyLine</description>
		<image>VietSkyLine</image>
	</bullet>
	<bullet>
		<title>Cute kittens</title>
		<date>August 2013</date>
		<description>Adopted 2 adorable kittens</description>
		<image>Cat</image>
	</bullet>
	<bullet>
		<title>Embedded Hardware Design</title>
		<date>July 2013</date>
		<description>Started Embedded Hardware Design</description>
		<image>Hardware</image>
	</bullet>
<!-- 	<bullet>
		<date>March 2013</date>
		<description>Adopted a cute snake</description>
		<image>Snake</image>
	</bullet> -->
	<bullet>
		<title>Embedded Software</title>
		<date>December 2012</date>
		<description>Started Embedded Software</description>
		<image>FirstEmbeddedSw</image>
	</bullet>
	<bullet>
		<title>Guitar</title>
		<date>January 2012</date>
		<description>Started playing guitar</description>
		<image>Guitar</image>
	</bullet>
</overview>
